In the window of the library, find the file folder of the virtual model.
Open the search bar of the virtual model to match the virtual model.
After entering the virtual model, we will use the linear virtual model tool to draw and remove the whiteboard on the model.
Click on the model to create a starting point.
In the drawing process, press the Ctrl key and click on the model to create a starting point.
Release the Ctrl key and click on the virtual model.
The virtual model can re-create a starting point.
In the drawing process, press the Shift key and click on the corresponding position to create a starting point along the vertical or horizontal direction.
Draw a figure along the virtual model curve.
The virtual model can be drawn using the same pattern.
Again click on the starting point to complete a closed figure.
Select the flat flat board.
Click on the figure that needs to be flat as a board.
Press the enter key to remove the board.
You can see the board generated in the 2D to 3D window.
And you can see the 2D and 3D windows.
You can see the 2D and 3D windows.
And we can see the 3D and 3D windows in this video.
In the 2D window background, click the mouse button and select Add background image
Click the Moon button to select the appropriate image
After selecting the image, click the Open button
Click and drag the background image to the model to make it easier to arrange later
After completion, click OK
In the mouse group, select the rectangle tool
Click the 2D window button to see the 2D window button
In the 2D window, click the mouse button and drag the mouse button to freely arrange the rectangle image
Arrange the rectangle image as close as possible to the image
Open the mouse button to complete the creation of the image
If the image is blocked, you can choose to hide the texture of the image
Make the margin of the original image
Use the plus and minus points division tool to create a straight line point at the appropriate position
Click and hold the left button on the line and a straight line point will be generated at the position
Use the edit panel tool to adjust the points and lines on the panel
Hello everyone
Click on the point you want to delete in the selection
and delete it with the Delete key.
Click and drag a straight line to move it to the right position.
Select the tool to edit the curve.
Right-click on a straight line and drag it.
You can change the straight line to a curve.
The curve created will be shown as a red dot.
You can adjust its position by dragging the curve created.
Use the adjustment panel tool to adjust the entire panel.
After clicking on the selected panel, right-click and select Copy in the pop-up menu.
Right-click again and select Paste in the pop-up menu.
It will appear as the mouse moves.
You can delete the paste by pressing the ESC key.
Right-click and select Paste in the pop-up menu.
You can see the smart guide line of the mouse.
Or you can press the Shift key to move the mouse in the horizontal, vertical, and diagonal direction.
You can move the mouse in the horizontal, vertical, and diagonal direction.
After placing the mouse at the right position, loose the mouse key and confirm the motion.
Use the adjustment panel tool to continue adjusting the straight line.
In the same process, press Shift to move the mouse in all directions.
In the process of moving the mouse, press Ctrl to move it in the horizontal, vertical, and diagonal direction.
Adjust the rest of the curve points again
Only when you select the curve point tool can you see the red curve point
After setting up the creation template tool, select the multidirectional tool in the drop-down menu
Click on the creation start point
You can also refer to the smart guide line in the drawing process
You can also click on the point you want to create while the creation process
You can press the right mouse button to create a point
In the process of creating points
You can also press the right mouse button to create a point
Press the Ctrl key and left-click to create a curve.
Press the Ctrl key and left-click to create a new curve.
Click on the starting point to complete the closed pattern.
Change to the edit tool.
After selecting a line, right-click and select Expand in the menu.
The selected line will be displayed on the panel.
Change to the edit tool and place the remaining panels.
In the下拉菜单栏中,选择内部长方形。
Click on the starting point and left-click to create a curve.
After completing the curve, change to the edit tool and place the remaining panels.
In the right-click and place the remaining panels.
In the下拉菜单栏中,选择内部长方形。
Change to the edit tool and place the remaining panels.
Click on the second background to find the panels in the edit tool section.
Don't chose the panels separately between the panels,
change to the edit tool and place the remaining panels.
In the background, right-click and place the left mouse button and drag the mouse to select a single panel.
Change to the edit tool and place the remaining panels.
In the selected version, click the button and select the symmetrical version, the version and the sewing line in the menu.
The preview of the symmetrical version will appear, click and place it in the right place.
In the same process of moving, you can press the Shift key to move in all directions.
When a version of the symmetrical version is modified, the other version will also be changed at the same time.
If you want to change the process, press the ESC key to cancel the change.
Arrange the versions in order and then arrange them in the 3D window.
Click to display the 2D and 3D window buttons to return to the original window layout.
In the 2D background, click and place the 3D window button.
In the 2D window, click and place the 3D window button.
Select the 3D picture of the background and redo it to make the following.
The fire shows the Jewelry function in the 2D window.
In the 2D window, click and place the Jewelry function to return to the original window.